<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Normal Men</title>
    <link>https://www.peark.es/podcast/index.html</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2025</copyright>
    <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
    <itunes:owner>
    <itunes:email>doe_sank_5k@icloud.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <description>Normal Men is four guys talking about the news. We want to help explain what's happening in the world around us and have some laughs along the way. And we think you might enjoy hearing what we have to say, as long as you don't mind a bit of normalcy in a world without much of it.</description>
    <itunes:image href="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/normal-men-cover-v1-040925.png"/>
    <itunes:category text="News Commentary"/>

    <item>
      <title>Episode 23: Super Sicario</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>The Normal Men are back and covering it all this week. To start (0:00-17:30) we check in on the fighting game community before Soda Chat and learnings about the weird stuff they’re drinking up in Maine. George and Propter reminisce about A&W and the gang laughs at grocery stores. Next up, Elon’s unhealthy obsession with fertility and race, as well as some discussion of the very real shifts in global birth rates around the world (17:30-30:30). Speaker of the House Mike Johnson broke some news this week: the President is a snitch (30:30-42:45) and the all carrot no stick Republican governing theory turns its eye to Georgia manufacturing (42:45-57:30). Our government murdered 11 Venezuelans this week, and the Men discuss, followed by some conversation about movies ranging from the light-hearted to the troubling (57:30-1:19:30). </p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E23+-+Super+Sicario.mp3" length="1:19:35" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:19:35</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 22: Talkin' 'Bout The Noles</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>Join the Normal Men for a break in the midst of Labor Day weekend for some college football chat and a victory lap celebrating Lowtax’s beloved Florida State University Seminoles (0:00-12:00). Next we talk Senate primaries and Senior Maine Correspondent Ed explains why Maine is actually a very large state, George commemorates one of our strongest Representatives, and the Men talk through the doomed logistics of applying tariffs to packages (12:00-42:00). Next up, it’s Glonzo time as Propter leads a discussion about the health of the President (42:00-51:00). Then it’s on to LLMs and why they’re such efficient mechanisms for cooking your brain (51:00-1:19:00). Finally a little Labor Day roundup of how each of the Men intended to spend their day off, including bachelor life, woodworking, grilling, potty training, and an anecdote about how seriously the state of Georgia takes college football (1:19:00-1:31:00).</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E22+-+Talkin'+'Bout+The+Noles.mp3" length="1:31:02" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E22</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 3 Sep 2025 0:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:31:02</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 21: Duck Duck ICE ft. Musicology Duck</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>Kick back with your heavily caffeinated beverage of choice as the boys dive into the world of canned stimulants (0:00 to 20:00). This week we’ve got Musicology Duck on to share some of her experiences from the streets of DC amidst a federal occupation of the nation’s capital (20:00 to 1:03:00). We also dive into President Trump’s efforts to take control of interest rates by an attempt to remove Governor Lisa Cook from the Federal Reserve’s Board of Governors (1:03:00 to 1:32:15) before a review of a landmark election result in Iowa (1:32:15 to end).</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E21+-+Duck+Duck+ICE+ft.+Musicology+Duck.mp3" length="1:37:54" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E21</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:37:54</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 20: The Last Great American Occupation ft. Lucy</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>The Men start this week talking about our fears, including heights, creepy-crawlies, and amoebas (from 0:00-5:40). Then: we’re going to Swift School this week as the Normal Men get up to speed on Taylor Swift and why we should pay more attention to her career (from 6:00-43:00). Then it’s time to chat about the large number of federal law enforcement officers and National Guard troops who have descended on the nation’s capital (from 43:00-1:05:00. Finally, we are unfortunately putting a few notable Democrats on flub watch. (1:05:00 to end)</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E20+-+The+Last+Great+American+Occupation+ft.+Lucy.mp3" length="1:21:04" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E20</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:21:04</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 19: Chat-GLP</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>This week your Normal Men are taking a trip to the UK for a garden party, which gives us the opportunity to discuss one of the most important - and impotent - thinkers on the Silicon Valley right. We’re also putting a Danish spin on things this week with an unfortunate story about what they’re doing in zoos over there. Finally, we chat at length about GLP-1s and the peptide revolution, including our own Propter’s experience with two different versions of the weight loss drugs.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E19+-+Chat-GLP.mp3" length="1:24:07" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E19</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:24:07</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 18: Ignorance Is BLS ft. Layla al-Sheikh</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>The Normal Men are thrilled to welcome Layla al-Sheikh, a Palestinian scholar and activist, to help us understand the political roots of the genocide in Gaza and the path forward towards a Palestinian state. Then we get to talk about the nitty-gritty of the US labor market’s statistical system after some significant developments. Also on the menu: Disco Elysium, a defense of Oracle, and discussion of two of the biggest freaks inside the Trump Administration’s impressive roster of degenerates. You can follow Layla on Bluesky @diplomatofnight.com and her work is also available at to-our-land.ghost.io.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E18+-+Ignorance+Is+BLS+ft.+Layla+al-Sheikh.mp3" length="1:30:04" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E18</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:30:04</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 17: Ordering In, Hulking Out ft. Josie Riesman</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>This week the boys dive deep into food delivery and the political, economic, and technological forces that drive it…and the discourse around it. We’re also lucky to be joined by Josie Riesman, the author of the definitive book on wrestling promoter Vince McMahon. She helps us understand the role that Hulk Hogan specifically and wrestling played in shaping our politics and culture. You can follow her on Bluesky @josie.zone. Her work can also be found at <a href="https://josie.zone/">josie.zone</a> including Ringmaster: Vince McMahon And The Unmaking of America. Please note George’s audio sucks for this one and we’re really sorry about that but Ed has promised us the mics are in the mail.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E17+-+Ordering+In%2C+Hulking+Out+ft.+Josie+Riesman.mp3" length="1:19:29" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E17</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:19:29</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 16: The Shadowy Hand of the Brooklyn DSA</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>The Normal Men discuss the toxic effects on democracy and growth of high income inequality and the means of maintaining it (including crypto). Also on the docket: more Epstein and Glonzo discussion and regretfully a review of why New York politicians are being so weird.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E16+-+The+Shadowy+Hand+of+the+Brooklyn+DSA.mp3" length="1:20:14" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E16</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:20:14</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 15: Les Givrals Was Lost In A Poker Game Ft. Swolecialism</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>GOLIKEHELLMACHINE is back with a new recurring segment! The Men are also joined by one of their Normal friends to talk about the unhinged world of Texas politics. Also up for discussion: MacArthur Park in Los Angeles and the world of immigration.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E15+-+Les+Givrals+Was+Lost+In+A+Poker+Game.mp3" length="1:07:26" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E15</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 13:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:07:26</itunes:duration>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Episode 14: Caked Up</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>It was a pretty rough week as far as news goes so the boys focus on the lighter things in life: unhinged Twitter accounts transvestigating NFL running backs, the best mass transit system south of DC, the meaningful victories for Congressional staffs that kept bad stuff out of the Republican reconciliation bill, and the latest bonfire of Elon Musk’s vanity known as the America Party. We also have full analysis of what emerged from the Senate and its brutal implications for American society.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E14+-+Caked+Up.mp3" length="1:18:32" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E14</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 9 Jul 2025 01:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:18:32</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13: (You Can't) Escape From New York Ft. Detective Pikajew</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>The Normal Men welcome New York political observer and union activist Detective Pikajew to chat about the huge win for Zohran Mamdani in that city’s mayoral primary as well as some union business. Also: loaded words and their definitions, an extremely bad Supreme Court case, and Tillis taps out in the Old North State. Follow our guest Detective Pikajew on Bluesky @clapifyoulikeme.favrd.social</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E13+-+(You+Can't)+Escape+From+New+York+Ft.+Detective+Pikajew.mp3" length="1:17:52" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E13</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 3 Jul 2025 01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:17:52</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12: One Man Out, One Man In</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>We say good bye (for now) to one of the Men before welcoming a new Man in his stead. The updated quartet then gets down to business discussing the US attack on Iran, the information environment, and the best ways to use AI.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      <p>The Normal Men are supporting Time Out Youth via a Prideraiser during June! For every goal Charlotte FC (soccer team) scores in June, pledge a donation amount. At the end, you'll donate the pledge amount multiplied by the goals scored. A pledge link is available at <a href="https://peark.es/prideraiser/">peark.es/prideraiser</a>!</p> 
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E12+-+One+Man+Out%2C+One+Man+In.mp3" length="1:05:57" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E12</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 18:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:05:57</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 11: Something Good Is Happening Somewhere</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>One of the Normal Men has to go on hiatus, but three soldier on to talk about a vegan on a rampage, Israel's attack on Iran, No Kings Day protests, and the disconnect between national politics and local reaction.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      <p>The Normal Men are supporting Time Out Youth via a Prideraiser during June! For every goal Charlotte FC (soccer team) scores in June, pledge a donation amount. At the end, you'll donate the pledge amount multiplied by the goals scored. A pledge link is available at <a href="https://peark.es/prideraiser/">peark.es/prideraiser</a>!</p> 
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E11+-+Something+Good+Is+Happening+Somewhere.mp3" length="1:02:00" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:02:00</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10: Faine Would I Fly, Yet Fear I To Fall</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>We welcome our first guest, Faine Greenwood, to talk about drones, the Musk-Trump divorce, and the origins of the most normal meme on Bluesky.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      <p>The Normal Men are supporting Time Out Youth via a Prideraiser during June! For every goal Charlotte FC (soccer team) scores in June, pledge a donation amount. At the end, you'll donate the pledge amount multiplied by the goals scored. A pledge link is available at <a href="https://peark.es/prideraiser/">peark.es/prideraiser</a>!</p> 
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E10+-+Faine+Would+I+Fly%2C+Yet+Fear+I+To+Fall.mp3" length="52:58" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E10</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>52:58</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9: De Cuckstoel Es Bezet</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>This week, we talk about Elon Musk (again) and his drugs, what his missteps mean for DOGE, new news on tariffs, and the Trump Administration’s war on the legal system.</p>
      
      <p>For show notes, links to our socials, and a transcript of this episode, check out <a href="https://normalmenpodcast.com/">normalmenpodcast.com</a>!</p>
      <p>The Normal Men are supporting Time Out Youth via a Prideraiser during June! For every goal Charlotte FC (soccer team) scores in June, pledge a donation amount. At the end, you'll donate the pledge amount multiplied by the goals scored. A pledge link is available at <a href="https://peark.es/prideraiser/">peark.es/prideraiser</a>!</p> 
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E09+-+De+Cuckstoel+Es+Bezet.mp3" length="57:30" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E09</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 5 Jun 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>57:30</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8: To All The Truck I've Loved Before</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>Content Warning: This episode features a frank discussion of political violence. In this week’s show, we talk about Lowtax Speedrun Enjoyer’s limitless Jeep enthusiasm. We also get into a serious conversation about recent political violence in the United States (and why it’s bad), and discuss the finer points of the doomed-to-be-rewritten House Republican budget bill.</p>
      
      <p>Follow us on Bluesky!<br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/peark.es">@peark.es</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/proptermalone.bsky.social">@proptermalone.bsky.social</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/rickywlmsbong.bsky.social">@rickywlmsbong.bsky.social</a><br />
      <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/golikehellmachine.com">@golikehellmachine.com</a></p>
        
      <p>You can also read GLHM's <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/work-is-four-letters/">Work Is Four Letters</a> and <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/doge-is-four-letters/">DOGE Is Four Letters</a>.</p>
      <p>A full transcript of the show is available <a href="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E08+-+To+All+The+Truck+I've+Loved+Before.txt">here</a>.</p>      
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E08+-+To+All+The+Truck+I've+Loved+Before.mp3" length="1:09:20" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E08</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:09:20</itunes:duration>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Episode 7: A Very Moody Episode</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>This week, we get into some of the details of the Moody’s US credit downgrade, and have updates on last week’s Supreme Court decision on the American Enemies Act. Finally, we talk about the world’s Chief Weeb for Boers, Elon Musk, and how his chatbot went floridly insane.</p>
      
      <p>Follow us on Bluesky!<br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/peark.es">@peark.es</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/proptermalone.bsky.social">@proptermalone.bsky.social</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/rickywlmsbong.bsky.social">@rickywlmsbong.bsky.social</a><br />
      <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/golikehellmachine.com">@golikehellmachine.com</a></p>
        
      <p>You can also read GLHM's <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/work-is-four-letters/">Work Is Four Letters</a> and <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/doge-is-four-letters/">DOGE Is Four Letters</a>.</p>
      <p>A full transcript of the show is available <a href="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E07+-+A+Very+Moody+Episode.txt">here</a>. We promise we'll make this prettier at some point.</p>      
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E07+-+A+Very+Moody+Episode.mp3" length="49:11" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E07</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>49:11</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6: Dad Joke Quotas</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>This week, George returns from Greece, Lowtax Speedrun Enjoyer demands that the new Pope defend the honor of his people, we talk about some good news from North Carolina, bad news for Congressional Republicans, and discuss the newest dysfunctional alcoholic joining the second Trump Administration. Propter Malone and GOLIKEHELLMACHINE exhaust their weekly allotment of dad(bad) jokes.</p>
      
      <p>Follow us on Bluesky!<br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/peark.es">@peark.es</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/proptermalone.bsky.social">@proptermalone.bsky.social</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/rickywlmsbong.bsky.social">@rickywlmsbong.bsky.social</a><br />
      <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/golikehellmachine.com">@golikehellmachine.com</a></p>
        
      <p>You can also read GLHM's <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/work-is-four-letters/">Work Is Four Letters</a> and <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/doge-is-four-letters/">DOGE Is Four Letters</a>.</p>
      <p>A full transcript of the show is available <a href="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E06+-+Dad+Joke+Quotas.txt">here</a>. We promise we'll make this prettier at some point.</p>      
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E06+-+Dad+Joke+Quotas.mp3" length="1:10:48" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E06</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2025 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:10:48</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5: Mister Pervert And Marble Abs</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>In this episode, George joins the gang from Greece to talk about normal — and abnormal — men. We also get into what’s going on the world’s most hacked group chat software, and we close out with a brief explanation of quarterly corporate filings including what they’re saying about the economy as it stares down the barrel of tariffs.</p>
      
      <p>Follow us on Bluesky!<br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/peark.es">@peark.es</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/proptermalone.bsky.social">@proptermalone.bsky.social</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/rickywlmsbong.bsky.social">@rickywlmsbong.bsky.social</a><br />
      <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/golikehellmachine.com">@golikehellmachine.com</a></p>
        
      <p>You can also read GLHM's <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/work-is-four-letters/">Work Is Four Letters</a> and <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/doge-is-four-letters/">DOGE Is Four Letters</a>.</p>
      <p>A full transcript of the show is available <a href="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E05+-+Mister+Pervert+And+Marble+Abs+-+Transcript.txt">here</a>. We promise we'll make this prettier at some point.</p>      
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E05+-+Mister+Pervert+And+Marble+Abs.mp3" length="45:47" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E05</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 7 May 2025 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>45:47</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4: Our Slutty Little Shorts</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>This week’s show is a bit on the lighter side. It’s spring time so we’re skies out thighs out before the boys do a round-up of the cabinet clownshows and calamities that are already defining the second Trump Administration. It’s also time for some Truck Talk given the new EV pickup company that emerged from stealth last week. Finally, the most normal story of the week: Shadeur Sanders.</p>
      
      <p>Follow us on Bluesky!<br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/peark.es">@peark.es</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/proptermalone.bsky.social">@proptermalone.bsky.social</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/rickywlmsbong.bsky.social">@rickywlmsbong.bsky.social</a><br />
      <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/golikehellmachine.com">@golikehellmachine.com</a></p>
        
      <p>You can also read GLHM's <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/work-is-four-letters/">Work Is Four Letters</a> and <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/doge-is-four-letters/">DOGE Is Four Letters</a>.</p>
      <p>A full transcript of the show is available <a href="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E04+-+Our+Slutty+Little+Shorts+-+Transcript.txt">here</a>. We promise we'll make this prettier at some point.</p>      
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E04+-+Our+Slutty+Little+Shorts.mp3" length="1:01:34" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E04</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:01:34</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    

    <item>
      <title>Episode 3: Murk The Yanks</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>A very normal Canadian election calls for some very Normal Men to talk about it. We also catch up on all the horrible effects of DOGE (which do not include lower government spending. Also: another update on Kilmar Ábrego García.</p>
      
      <p>Follow us on Bluesky!<br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/peark.es">@peark.es</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/proptermalone.bsky.social">@proptermalone.bsky.social</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/rickywlmsbong.bsky.social">@rickywlmsbong.bsky.social</a><br />
      <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/golikehellmachine.com">@golikehellmachine.com</a></p>
        
      <p>You can also read GLHM's <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/work-is-four-letters/">Work Is Four Letters</a> and <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/doge-is-four-letters/">DOGE Is Four Letters</a>.</p>
      <p>A full transcript of the show is available <a href="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E03+-+Murk+The+Yanks+-+Transcript.txt">here</a>. We promise we'll make this prettier at some point.</p>      
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E03+-+Murk+The+Yanks.mp3" length="1:09:40" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E03</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:09:40</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: Dunkirk For Treats</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>In this week's episode of Normal Men, your very normal hosts are joined by an inspiring special guest before we talk about tariffs and bonds, because tariffs and bonds are going to continue to be big news for the foreseeable future (nobody is happy about this).  We also discuss updates in the Kilmar Ábrego García case and the effort to overturn an election to the North Carolina Supreme Court.</p>
      
      <p>Follow us on Bluesky!<br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/peark.es">@peark.es</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/proptermalone.bsky.social">@proptermalone.bsky.social</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/rickywlmsbong.bsky.social">@rickywlmsbong.bsky.social</a><br />
      <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/golikehellmachine.com">@golikehellmachine.com</a></p>
        
      <p>You can also read GLHM's <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/work-is-four-letters/">Work Is Four Letters</a> and <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/doge-is-four-letters/">DOGE Is Four Letters</a>.</p>
      <p>A full transcript of the show is available <a href="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E02+-+Dunkirk+For+Treats+-+Transcript.txt">here</a>. We promise we'll make this prettier at some point.</p>      
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E02+-+Dunkirk+For+Treats.mp3" length="1:12:35" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E02</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:11:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1: Our Beautiful Tariffs, Something's Happening Out There, and Immigration Is Getting Scary</title>
      <itunes:author>George Pearkes</itunes:author>
      <description><p>Welcome to the first episode of Normal Men. George and Propter introduce the podcast and what we're trying to do here, and are joined by Lowtax (not that one) and Go Like Hell Machine to discuss tariffs, the Hands Off protests, and the case of Kilmar Ábrego García.</p>
      
      <p>Follow us on Bluesky!<br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/peark.es">@peark.es</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/proptermalone.bsky.social">@proptermalone.bsky.social</a><br /><a href="https://bsky.app/profile/rickywlmsbong.bsky.social">@rickywlmsbong.bsky.social</a><br />
      <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/golikehellmachine.com">@golikehellmachine.com</a></p>
        
      <p>You can also read GLHM's <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/work-is-four-letters/">Work Is Four Letters</a> and <a href="https://golikehellmachine.com/doge-is-four-letters/">DOGE Is Four Letters</a>.</p>
      </description>
      <enclosure url="https://pearkes-podcast-files.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/Normal+Men+-+S01E01+-+Our+Beautiful+Tariffs%2C+Something's+Happening+Out+There%2C+and+Immigration+Is+Getting+Scary.mp3" length="1:11:51" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://www.peark.es/podcast/S01E01</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1:11:51</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    
    <!-- Add more episodes here -->
  </channel>
</rss>
